Having a newborn can be daunting.
有一个新生儿可能会令人生畏。
What do you need to buy?
你需要买些什么呢？
How will you get the baby to sleep?
你要如何让宝宝入睡呢？
And how will you pay for everything?
你要如何支付所有的费用呢？
Could the answers to these worries lie in a 'baby box'?
解决这些烦恼的答案会在一个“婴儿礼盒”里吗？
The baby box has taken the world by storm, but what is it?
婴儿礼盒已经风靡全球，但它究竟是什么呢？
Well, it originated in Finland in the 1930s as a kind of maternity kit for expectant parents provided by the government.
嗯，它起源于20世纪30年代的芬兰，是政府提供给准父母的一种产妇用品套装。
The box contains supplies, such as bibs, nappies, and teething toys.
这个礼盒包含有围嘴、尿布和出牙期玩具等用品。
It also comes with a small mattress, which is placed in the bottom of the box to create the baby's first cot.
它还配有一个小床垫，这个床垫被放在礼盒底部，就成了宝宝的第一张婴儿床。
Now, the idea of putting a child to sleep in a box may shock some.
现在，把孩子放在礼盒里睡觉的想法可能会让一些人感到震惊。
But, experts say this could reduce the risks that come with babies sleeping in the same bed as their parents.
但是，专家说这可以降低宝宝和父母睡在同一张床上所带来的风险。
The box has been a huge success and is said to be one of the main reasons why the rate of infant mortality in Finland is so low.
这个礼盒取得了巨大的成功，据说它也是为什么芬兰婴儿死亡率如此之低的主要原因之一。
A few years ago, stories of the Finnish baby box went viral.
几年前，芬兰婴儿礼盒的故事迅速传播开来。
Other countries around the world have since caught onto the idea and adapted to suit local needs.
从那以后，世界上其他国家也开始接受这个主意，并调整以适应当地的需求。
For example, in South Africa, the box is made of plastic and can be used as a bath rather than a bed.
例如，在南非，这种礼盒是用塑料制成的，被用来当澡盆，而不是婴儿床。
The main objective, however, is to encourage mothers to attend antenatal classes during their pregnancy.
然而，其主要目的是鼓励准妈妈们在怀孕期间参加产前课程。
The version trialled in India includes other appropriate supplies, such as a mosquito net to protect babies from malaria.
在印度试用的版本里还包括其他适宜的日常用品，比如一个用来保护宝宝免受疟疾侵害的蚊帐。
In Canada, additions to the baby box include a "crib-side assistance booklet" to help fathers bond with their baby.
在加拿大，婴儿礼盒里增加了一本“婴儿床边辅助手册”，以帮助爸爸们与宝宝建立亲密关系。
Written in the style of a car-repair manual, the booklet offers first-time dads helpful advice on matters such as how to burp their child.
这本手册采用汽车维修手册的风格编写，为准爸爸们在如何给孩子拍嗝等问题上提供了有用的建议。
Of course, the baby box can only do so much.
当然，婴儿礼盒能做的只有这么多。
Many believe governments should focus on providing parents with adequate maternity leave and paternity leave and improving health care and education.
许多人认为政府应该专注于为准父母们提供足够的产假和陪产假，并改善医疗保健和教育条件。
Good things come in small packages though, and for such a simple idea the baby box really does tick a lot of boxes!
不过，好东西往往藏于小包装中，对于这样一个简单的想法，婴儿礼盒确实满足了很多需求！